only people that own pitbulls are the
ones that are like they're the best dog
ever you need to open up your heart like
no I'll trust you from a fire cuz I have
a couple friends here's the thing I have
a couple of friends that love pimples
and I go to his house and actually one
of my cousins and I go to his house it's
so scary because like when I show up at
the house the dog is already waiting for
me at the screen like right and I see
him in his living room like yell come
let me in he was like the doors open
just come in I was like nah man won't
you just come let me in right cuz the
dog is ripping at the screen right he's
like yo the dogs nannies do anything
just come in I'm like well he's ripped
his screen to pieces I don't know if I
want to walk by him right now so he
angrily comes to the door come on
watch out just a dog to watch out the
dog obviously listens to him cuz he
feeds it so the dog to me looks like a
monster to him the doesn't backs up my
guard Cesar Millan okay go ahead back
your dog up dog backs up he comes he
geek he's like hearted man I'm staying
really close to the hoenn league' right
on his play when we go in a house
he's like you got to relax man the dog
can smell fear I was like well he can
definitely notice be running down my leg
right now there's I am afraid right now
straight-up afraid the other dog lifted
you off your feet why is telling you
because the dog never smells an area
buddy you don't care about right
[Music]
immediately when I get in the house the
dogs
I'm trying to act tough hey it's alright
dog it's okay
I'm so scared
the dog hear my heart beating right now
I am a Friday - right now it's always
weird when people say stuff like that -
like just just act a certain way act
tough like they say the same thing with
bears go like if there's a bear
attacking you in the woods you play dead
I'm like what's the Bears qualifications
for knowing if you're dead
cuz I'm definitely gonna he's hitting me
I'm definitely though like does that
mean cuz I could keep my eyes closed
when I do that
here's a beer slapping now they're like
hey
bears just slapping me around I'm like
I'm the best charades player
[Music]
do we messed up who steals like one
smart bear out there just put his little
paw on your neck like no who still has a
pulse
watch my entire special for $0.99 or
just watch more clips check out more
clips click one of them you got to check
it out now if I were you I'd probably
click the $0.99 one because that goes
right into my pocket click one click it
click it click lick lick lick lick lick
lick lick lick lick lick lick lick lick
lick okay